{
    "id": "7d5bcd3705fb4f27b7ebe501d1d7b473",
    "title": "Sentence Completion",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "……………………. it prove to be true, I shall resign from my job.",
            "description": "Should is often used instead of if in conditional clauses to express the idea that something is very unlikely. ",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "Would",
                "Should",
                "Were"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………… it possible, I would buy that apartment.",
            "description": "Were is often used in the second conditional to talk about improbable situations. ",
            "answers": [
                "Were",
                "If",
                "Should"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "If you exercised regularly, you ………………………… become strong and healthy.",
            "description": "In the second conditional we use a simple past tense in the if-clause and would + first form of the verb in the main clause.",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "would",
                "would have"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The more he studies, ………………………",
            "description": "The same structure is used in both clauses. ",
            "answers": [
                "he understands less",
                "less he understands",
                "the less he understands"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Is she ……………………….. to be a grandmother?",
            "description": "As an adverb enough is used after the adjective it modifies. ",
            "answers": [
                "enough old",
                "old enough"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The strike continued ……………………… two weeks.",
            "description": "For indicates duration.",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She has been staying with her parents ………………………. January.",
            "description": "We use since to indicate the starting point.",
            "answers": [
                "from",
                "for",
                "since"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………….. having many faults, he was actually a nice guy.",
            "description": "Despite is a preposition. It is used before a noun or ing form.",
            "answers": [
                "Although",
                "In spite",
                "Despite"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………… she was not perfect, I couldn’t help admiring her.",
            "description": "Although is a conjunction. Use it before a clause.",
            "answers": [
                "Despite",
                "However",
                "Although"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I felt like ………………………… but I didn’t dare to.",
            "description": "We use an ing form after felt like.",
            "answers": [
                "laugh",
                "to laugh",
                "laughing"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "We didn’t have any trouble ……………………….. him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to find",
                "finding",
                "to finding"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "If you don’t understand, don’t hesitate ………………………. questions.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to ask",
                "ask",
                "asking"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}